<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Short Stories on Kit Kron</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Short Stories on Kit Kron</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 10:20:54 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Under the I-5 Outside Redding, California</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/i5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 10:20:54 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/i5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;title&gt;Under the I-5 Outside Redding, California&lt;/title&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cars rushed by. The sun glared down at me, mocking me. I think it knew how much it irritated me, at least that’s what it felt like. I was under a tiny bridge that supported a small section of the I-5 in central California, just outside of Redding. I had been hitchhiking my way to San Diego to see a few friends. That was no longer my goal. The grasshoppers and crickets made long, droning chirps around me. I had never been this uncomfortable. It made me want to claw at my skin. Yet I couldn’t move, and I hadn’t been able to move for some time, ever since that car came out of nowhere and shoved me down into this miserable hole. The sun was burning itself into my vision. I wished more than anything that I could shut my eyes, but they wouldn’t budge. It made it worse that I could feel everything. I could feel my leg bending backwards under me, the bone poking out like a jagged knife. I could feel my shattered spine and how my ribs punctured my lungs. My intestines hung out of my abdomen. My brain was exposed to the elements. I couldn’t stop thinking about how frightening a sight I must be.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Guide to the Crude Dissection of a Body</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/body/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 10:20:43 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/body/</guid>
      <description>&lt;title&gt;A Guide to the Crude Dissection of a Body&lt;/title&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At first glance, it may seem trivial. You’re not a doctor, nor are you trained in human anatomy, yet you feel certain that you’ll be able to carry out the act. Take it step by step. Move your hands slowly and methodically. There is no need for absolute precision, but striving for it may be a good idea. Check off the list in your mind before you begin. Grab your gloves and lay them out and slide your hands into the formed rubber and pull them taught and inspect them for wrinkles or holes or signs of damage. Go through your tools, your saws and scalpels and forceps, all second hand, all slightly rusted. Make sure your clothes are ones you intend to dispose of, a shirt filled with holes and a pair of jeans with no button or zipper held up by a crudely made belt made of rope. There is no need for sanitation. There is no life to be saved, only knowledge to be gained. Your check list is complete; there is nothing more to prepare. Take a breath. Look at the eyes. Understand what you are about to do and exploit it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Memory of a Field</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/fieldmem/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 10:12:50 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/fieldmem/</guid>
      <description>&lt;title&gt;A Memory of a Field&lt;/title&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I remember being in a field, surrounded by tall dry grass, staring at that house. My mom stood a few feet behind me, both of us standing silently, observing the landscape around us. We were on our way to a backpacking trail, one that my mom had visited a few times before, but we had stopped briefly on our way there to look at the small lake that broke up the field, and more specifically for her, to take a break from driving. My mom suddenly broke the silence that had been lingering for a while, saying something about the lake or the mountains or the field, but not the house. I answered absentmindedly, saying something small in acknowledgement. I couldn’t shift my focus from the house. It was decrepit, but not completely. Its shingles were falling off and its wood was rotting, but it wasn’t caving in, and it wasn’t blown over. It felt like someone was maintaining it. That scared me, but I’m not sure why. My mom finally addressed the house, telling me that it looked like a “murder cabin”. I agreed, it really did look like a house straight out of a horror movie, but that also didn’t quite do it justice. The house had something more haunting about it, something that awoke a deep fear within me, yet it also brought a heavy sense of melancholy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quercus Robur</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/quercusrobur/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:08:03 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/quercusrobur/</guid>
      <description>&lt;title&gt;Quercus Robur&lt;/title&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I awoke in a chair. A wooden chair, made from birch, with a table made from hickory in front of me. There was someone across from me, staring at me intently. I gazed around. I was in a coffee shop, but there was nothing but a small cedar counter on the other side of the store. The person across from me and I were sitting at the only table in the store. The walls were made out of cement, and they were covered in scratches. I believed I had been here before. The windows at the front of the store showed only pure white outside. I hated it. I drew my attention to the other person. I gazed at their face for a brief moment, and it seemed wrong. Their eyes were swapped, and their nose was different. Their skin was course, and I could sense the bugs under it, burrowing in and out of their flesh and forming tunnels. I hoped the bugs wouldn’t notice me. The person shot me a look suddenly. I couldn’t quite tell what they meant by it, so I was afraid that they were upset. “Your makeup looks off today”, they told me. I covered my face, embarrassed. “You don’t have to be rude about it, I tried my best”, I said. I lifted my hands away from my face. They were covered in blood, unsurprisingly. I had spent hours getting ready, making sure that everything was just the way I wanted, but my skills were limited. Why did they have to point that out? I took out my phone and used its camera to look at myself.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I am a house.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/iamahouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 18:04:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/iamahouse/</guid>
      <description>&lt;title&gt;I am a house.&lt;/title&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am a house. A house that cannot feel. A house that emotions cannot attach to, and that, when perceived, cannot be projected upon. A house that leaves people’s minds the moment I am not being observed. I can never be remembered, and no feeling can describe me. Every time I try to internalize something, it cannot be absorbed into my infested walls and moldy floors, for they reject anything that would make me more than just an empty house. I try so hard to feel, to have people feel for me, force emotions upon me in an attempt to become something more than I am, but I am rotten. As more years pass and time marches forward, I degrade even more, mold consumes every inch of me and rust makes my bolts stiff and red, and no matter how hard I try, I cannot feel. I contemplated collapsing in on myself; to let my walls keel over and my furniture shatter, to let the termites hollow me out and release me from the pursuit of feeling, but I can’t give up. For some incomprehensible reason, I can’t give up. And one day, my waiting came to an end.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
